minitime.com 2019-08-03

# Privacy Policy - MiniTime

#### MINITIME PRIVACY STATEMENT

This privacy statement describes the privacy-related practices of MiniTime, Inc. ("MiniTime", "our", "us" or "we"), in connection with website located at [http://www.MiniTime.com](http://www.minitime.com/) (the "Site"), and the services made available by MiniTime through the Site (collectively, the "Service"). 

#### What Information We Collect 

The types of information that we collect fall under two general categories: personally identifiable information ("PII") and non-personally identifiable information ("non-PII"). PII consists of any information which can be used to specifically contact or identify you as an individual, whereas non-PII consists of aggregate information or any information that does not reveal your identity or enable us to contact you. The following sections describe how your PII and non-PII are collected by us, and how we use and share such information. As used in this privacy statement, the terms "using" and "processing" information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally. 

#### How We Collect and Use Information 

PII. When you register for the Service and in the course of your use of the Service, we collect a variety of information about you, including, but not limited to your email address, name, city, state and country, ages of your child(ren), if applicable, photos or other content in which you can be identified or other PII you provide via a SNS (defined below). 

Registration. You may register directly via the Site or by logging into your account with certain third party social media or social networking sites ("SNS") (including, but not limited to, Facebook) via the Site, as described herein. If you decide to register through an SNS, we will extract the personal information you have provided to the SNS (such as your "real" name, email address and other information you make publicly available via the SNS) from the account you have with the applicable SNS and use that information to create your account for your use of the Service. The specific information that we extract may depend on the privacy settings you have with the SNS. You hereby consent to our access to and collection of such personal information about you. 

Email. We require an email address from you when you register for the Service. We use your email for both transactional (e.g., activity updates such as notices that another user is now following you on the Service) and promotional (e.g., newsletters, new product offerings, event notifications, special third-party offers) purposes. Email messages we send you may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the emails, including whether the email was opened and what links (if any) were clicked. If you would rather not receive promotional emails from us, please see the section below labeled "Choice/Opt-Out." We reserve the right to send you certain communications, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

Demographic Data. Demographic data is also collected via the Site. We use this data to tailor our visitors' experience, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. Some of this information may be shared with advertisers on a non-personally identifiable, aggregate basis. 

Online Survey Data. We may periodically conduct voluntary member surveys. We encourage our members to participate in such surveys because they provide us with important information regarding the improvement of the Service. You may also volunteer for certain surveys that we may offer to our users, and any additional rules regarding the conduct of such surveys will be disclosed to you prior to your participation. We do not link the survey responses to any PII, and all responses are anonymous. 

Information Regarding Your Friends. We offer contact access tools to help you access your friends' addresses so that you can find your friends on the Service, and invite your contacts who do not have MiniTime accounts to join our Service. We will send your designated contacts a one-time message containing your name and inviting them to visit the Site. These emails will also include instructions on how to remove their information from our database. 

Public Forums. We make discussion areas, public forums and other interactive areas of the Site available to our users and visitors. Any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and will be displayed in connection with your name, profile picture and city, state and country. 

Log Files. Any time you visit the Site, our servers automatically gather information from your browser (such as your IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks). This information may be used to analyze trends, administer the Site, prevent fraud, track visitor movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information. 

Cookies. We use "cookies" to keep track of some types of information while you are visiting the Site or using the Service. Cookies are very small files placed on your computer, and they allow us to count the number of visitors to our Site and distinguish repeat visitors from new visitors. They also allow us to save user preferences and track user trends. We rely on cookies for the proper operation of our website; therefore if your browser is set to reject all cookies, the Site will not function properly. Users who refuse cookies assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality. Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser. 

Google Analytics. We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how users use the Site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of our website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Site, compiling reports on website activity for our use and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. As stated above, you may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Service. By using the Site, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. 

Web Beacons. "Web beacons" (also known as "clear gifs" and "pixel tags") are small transparent graphic images that are often used in conjunction with cookies in order to further personalize our website for our users and to collect a limited set of information about our visitors. We may also use web beacons in email communications in order to understand the behavior of our customers. We do not link the web beacons to any PII. 

#### Disclosure of Your Information to Third Parties 

MiniTime Users. When you register through the Site and submit your Personal Information to create a profile webpage or when you make available content via the Site, MiniTime Users will see your name, profile photo, your city, state and country, ages of your child(ren), any content you choose to make available via the Site, including, but not limited to, photos and travel reviews and the names of any MiniTime Users you choose to follow via the Site. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information. 

Social Networking Services. The Site gives you the option to share information contained in your account with certain social networking services (including but not limited to Twitter and Facebook). We will not share your account information, which may contain your PII, with such social networking services unless you expressly authorize such disclosure. 

Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information. We may share aggregated information that does not include PII and we may otherwise disclose aggregate information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your PII. 

Service Providers. We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Site's features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Service are used. These third parties have access to your PII only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. 

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. MiniTime cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of MiniTime or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. 

Information Transferred As a Result of Sale of Business. MiniTime may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your PII, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. 

#### Third-Party Advertising 

We may use third-party advertising agencies or other service providers to serve ads on the Site on behalf of MiniTime, Inc. or third-party advertisers (e.g., retailers of goods or services). These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is completely anonymous and does not contain personally identifiable information. Some of these third-party advertising agencies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers you the option to opt out of ad targeting from its member agencies by following the procedures listed <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. We will only share your information with third parties in the ways defined in this privacy statement. 

#### Age Restrictions 

This Site is not directed to persons under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [http://help.MiniTime.com/customer/portal/emails/new](http://help.minitime.com/customer/portal/emails/new). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files. 

#### International Users 

If you reside outside the United States, your access to and use of the Site is at your own risk. Users may not access the Site, register for or use the Service if prohibited by law in their country of residence. Your information may be transferred to -- and maintained on -- computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, MiniTime transfers PII to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this privacy statement followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

#### Security 

We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information stored in our database. We will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, but given that no information transmitted over the Internet can be guaranteed 100% secure, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and hence accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure. We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored "personal data" (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on the Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system. 

#### Links to Other Sites 

Our Site contains links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by "clicking on" a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party's website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other websites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

#### Choice/Opt-Out 

You may use the following options for removing your information from our email database if you wish to opt out of receiving promotional emails and newsletters. 

  * Click on the "unsubscribe" link on the bottom of the email; 
  * Click on the "Account Settings" link from the Site home page, and un-check the undesired promotions. 
  * Click [here](http://help.minitime.com/customer/portal/emails/new) to let us know which promotional emails you wish to opt out of. 

#### Updating and Deleting Your Information 

You may change your email address, password and other information from the "Account Settings" page accessible via a link from the Site home page. To the extent you choose to include PII or other information in your profile, the Service allows you to update or remove that information by editing or deleting the content via the Site. If you would like us to delete your account in our system, please contact us [http://help.MiniTime.com/customer/portal/emails/new](http://help.minitime.com/customer/portal/emails/new) with a request that we delete your Personal Information from our database. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. 

#### Contacting MiniTime 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with us, you can contact us at [http://help.MiniTime.com/customer/portal/emails/new](http://help.minitime.com/customer/portal/emails/new). 

#### Modifications to this Privacy Statement 

This privacy statement may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new privacy statement on the Site. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes. Unless otherwise defined in this privacy statement, terms used in this privacy statement have the same meanings as in our MiniTime Terms of Use, accessible at www.MiniTime.com/terms-of-use. 

#### Effective Date 

This privacy statement was last revised on 3/01/2012.
